firstfederal.com 2019-05-22

# South State Privacy Notice | South State Bank

Regardless of changes in technology and information, South State Bank has always been-and will continue to be-committed to the principles of customer privacy. We understand that when you open an account with us, apply for a loan, or deal with us or one of our affiliated companies in any way, we ask you to provide us with private financial and personal information.

We honor the trust you place in us by maintaining the confidentiality and accuracy of that information, and we use it in manners consistent with the confidence you have placed in us. We will uphold both the letter and the spirit of federal and state laws as they relate to this important issue.

  * [Privacy Notice [PDF]](https://www.southstatebank.com/internet/wp-content/uploads/2019/01/SSB-Privacy-Notice-Rev-1.11.19.pdf "Privacy Notice")

We reserve the right to change this notice at any time by posting a new privacy policy notice. We encourage you to carefully review the notice and the choices it outlines. If you have already requested a change in your information sharing, you do not need to respond again. We will continue to honor your previous sharing preferences.

Rev. 01/19

**FACTS** | **WHAT DOES SOUTH STATE BANK  ** **DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**  
---|---  
**Why?** | Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.  
**What?** | The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include: 

  * Social Security number and income;
  * Account balances and transaction/payment history;
  * Employment information and credit history.

**How?** | All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons South State Bank chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.  
**Reasons we can share your personal information** | **Does South State Bank share?** | **Can you limit this sharing?**  
**For our everyday business purposes –**

such as: to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus

| Yes | No  
**For our marketing purposes –**

to offer our products and services to you

| Yes | Yes  
**For joint marketing with other financial companies** | Yes | Yes  
**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –**

information about your transactions and experiences

| Yes | No  
**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –**

information about your creditworthiness

| Yes | Yes  
**For our affiliates to market to you** | Yes | Yes  
**For nonaffiliates to market to you** | Yes | Yes  
**To limit our sharing** | 

  * Call Toll-free 1-800-277-2175;
  * Visit us online: www.southstatebank.com; or
  * Visit any branch office and speak with a bank representative.

**Please note:**

If you are a _new_ customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this notice. When you are _no longer_ our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.

However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.  
  
**Questions?** | Call toll-free 1-800-277-2175 or visit any branch to speak with a bank representative.  
**What We Do** |   
---|---  
**How does South State Bank protect my personal information?** | To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.  
**How does South State Bank collect my personal information?** | We collect your personal information, for example, when you 

  * Open an account, deposit money, or perform transactions;
  * Pay your bills or apply for a loan;
  * Use your credit or debit card.

We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.  
  
**Why can’t I limit all sharing?** | Federal law gives you the right to limit only 

  * Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthiness;
  * Affiliates from using your information to market to you;
  * Sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you.

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.  
  
**What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?** | Your choices will apply individually unless you tell us to also opt out other joint account holders.  
**Definitions** |   
---|---  
**Affiliates** | Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies. 

_Our affiliates include companies such as South State Corporation, SSB_ _  Properties, Inc., and South State Advisory, Inc._  
  
**Nonaffiliates** | Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies. 

  * _Nonaffiliates we share with can include credit card companies, mortgage servicing providers and marketing service providers so they can market to you._

**Joint Marketing** | A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you. 

  * _Our joint marketing partners include credit card companies, marketing service providers, investment companies and insurance companies._
